And he's ready, Señor.
A big change can be worthwhile.
And I just hope I can make you all proud
with this new project.
- Liam!
- Yes, you changed your life.
You rise to the top while we die one by one.
You should die before anyone else does!
Why did you do that to me?
I really can't remember anything.
You dazzled us with money that's so small
compared to what you'll gain.
You tore down
almost half of our neighborhood.
And you stole our livelihood!
Nestor Bartolome.
A resident of Verde Village.
The community
beside Casa Fuerte's Strongland Residences?
But that's how furious they are to me?
What did I do wrong to them?
Boss, I'm begging you.
Please, don't put my grandfather in prison.
Jail me instead.
If you need to imprison someone,
let it be me.
If you did something wrong,
I know there was a reason behind it.
Liam, you taught me
that everyone can have a second chance,
just like how you gave me
my second chance at happiness.
This time...
showing your weakness is not cowardice.
I thought everything would be better
if you were here.
Sometimes, life brings us
to an unexpected path.
To an uncertain place.
We don't know if it will lead us astray
or if it will bring us
to the right destination.
This is it. There's no turning back.
If you say so.
Liam Herrera, are you having second thoughts?
I just don't want to get rejected again.
They already turned this story down.
Wait, hold on.
You know...
They haven't read your whole story yet.
Yet they turned it down in just one call?
That's wrong.
So, they should read the whole pilot script.
So what do we do?
All the pilot scripts for review
are in the executive producer's office.
So we will include your script with the rest.
How do we get inside the producer's office?
We don't have access here.
Where did you get that?
Well, in case you forgot,
I've played bit roles in this TV network
many times.
So, I have connections.
Is that legal?
Let's just say
that you will become
one of the greatest writers
this TV network has known.
So let's go. You're gonna have to wear this.
Don't show my photo.
Just pretend it's your ID.
I'm famous here.
My face will be enough.
Let's go!
Really?
- This is what we'll do.
- What?
Over there is the office of Sir Mark, okay?
I'll distract the guard.
Just wait for my signal, okay?
Isn't that dangerous?
Ma'am, where are you going?
Joyce.
- Trinidad.
- Joyce!
- So it's you.
- Meynard.
It's me.
How can you forget my beautiful face?
- How are you?
- What are you doing here?
Meynard...
I'm just visiting.
You just finished taping your show, right?
Yes.
Did you watch our episode last night?
It was great.
- You were really great.
- I know, right?
- Yes.
- I knew it.
I deserve a better role
than "classmate number two", right?
I should play the best friend.
Joyce...
Don't forget about me once you become a star.
Of course, Meynard.
You're one of my favorites.
With your good looks...
There's someone. Meynard...
- Oh, he doesn't have an ID.
- Yes?
- I wonder what he needs.
- Where are you going?
Seventh floor, Sir.
Who are you looking for?
Well, I'm looking for Melvin.
Come on, hurry up. Someone might see us.
- Go.
- What do you mean?
- Put it there.
- Should I?
I'm sure that if Sir Mark reads your script,
he'll approve it.
He'll hire you as a writer.
You'll be a regular here.
They will produce your script, have a shoot,
and air it right away.
Then that's it!
You think?
Of course!
I believe in you.
You're the only one who encourages me.
Go. Do it.
- Here?
- Yes.
I thought someone was here.
I thought we would get caught.
We weren't caught, but...
We're locked in.
What?
See? It won't open.
How do we get out of here?
And in this world where I feel trapped...
I'm thankful that I found you again.
Joyce.
Joyce, I thought you weren't in this world.
You're getting married?
Who are you marrying?
- Joy...
- Do I know you?
Cut! My God, cut!
- What are you doing?
- Who's that guy?
- This is crazy!
- He ruined the scene.
Who's this guy messing with my set?
This is disappointing.
A set?
Yes, Mister. We're in a middle of a scene.
We're filming.
Filming?
Joyce, what's this?
Savana, do you know him?
I'm sorry, Director. I don't know him.
Savana?
What do you mean by "director"?
Yes, I'm the film director.
She's Savana.
And you're the pest
who's interrupting our set.
Where's crowd control? Crowd control!
Come!
Hurry up!
Get him out of here.
I told you already.
We're doing it again and again.
- Arvie!
- Yes, Director?
- From the top.
- Okay, Director.
- My God!
- Sorry, Director.
Okay, guys. Places.
From the top.
Talents!
Talents, hurry up! Fall in line.
Here.
Savana is so beautiful, right?
Yes, I thought she is a snob,
but she's so nice.
And she smells good.
I wish I'd get chosen to be her partner.
So, you are now known as "Savana".
That's why I can't find you.
Her name has been Savana ever since.
That's just her screen name, right?
Yes, but no one knew her name
when she was not famous yet.
She became known as Savana.
She's now a famous actress?
Have you been hiding under a rock
to be so clueless about Savana?
No...
I'm not into show business.
Why are you here if you don't like it?
- Right?
- Honestly, I just happened to pass by.
I thought there was a real wedding.
But tell me more about Savana.
She became famous
in this drama, Captive Hearts.
You're filming Captive Hearts?
Yes.
It's been running for years.
It's been on air for quite a while.
Seven years.
Savana's charm is really something.
You have fulfilled your dream, Joyce.
Guys.
- Guys, guys, guys.
- Yes, Director?
You're making my blood boil.
We need to find a good-looking guy
to be Savana's partner in the next scene.
- Okay.
- Okay? Wait...
I'll do it. I will choose the guy myself.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Where are they?
Here.
Okay.
Shrimp number one.
Okay?
Take note.
Try. Let me try.
Shrimp number two.
Okay, Director.
Okay?
This one...
Well, it's possible.
But... he's shrimp number three.
Okay?
Mister...
Why?
What?
What are you doing here?
Guys, what do you think our show is?
A cooking show?
You're sending me all these shrimps.
We'll just look for someone else.
Look for someone else, now.
- Hurry up.
- Hurry.
This is driving me nuts.
Do you know how to drive?
- Me?
- Yes.
No, our director.
Of course, you. I'm asking you.
- Yes, I do. Why?
- Okay, come here.
Come with me.
- What?
- Come on. Come with me.
Director, we already found someone.
Here he is.
He's good-looking, and he knows how to drive.
Hold on. Wait, wait.
Him? The guy who ruined our scene earlier?
Yes, Director. We have no one else...
I just happened to pass by.
Okay.
Let's try him.
- Teach him the lines.
- Yes, Director.
I don't want to do it over and over.
I will throw some lines at him
so he can memorize them.
- Go!
- Go, Riza. Go! Go!
- MJ, Macy...
- Let's go.
Put some makeup on him.
Hey, hey.
Hurry up.
What?
That's too long. I can't memorize that.
- Go, go, go. Places, everyone.
- I can dress on my own.
You're the man earlier, right?
Yes, Miss Savana.
I'm sorry if I'm not myself earlier.
The name you called me...
- Sorry?
- You called me by a different name.
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
Do you recognize me now, Jo...
Arvie! Let's start filming.
Stand by for take, actors!
ID, please.
ID, Captive Hearts!
- Rolling!
- Audio roll!
Sequence 22, take one!
Okay, ready!
Rolling!
- Rolling, Director!
- In three...
- Two...
- One...
Action!
Say your line!
Ma'am, are you okay?
Yes, Mister.
Everything happens for a reason.
What's worse...
is to spend the rest of your life with him,
but you are not happy.
Cut!
Lovely!
Cut! Good take! Next sequence!
We love you, Savana!
- Bye, Savana.
- Savana!
Savana! Savana!
Don't forget...
Don't miss the fans' day, okay?
Bring the tarps and everything.
See you there.
Hashtag Savana Forever!
Savana.
Can we talk?
- You again?
- Excuse me.
Look who we have here.
Savana's meet-and-greet isn't today.
She's tired. She had an early call time.
So let's go.
Mom?
What? What did you say?
You're beautiful in person, Aunt Joanne.
Come on.
Fine. I know you'll just ask for a selfie.
Go on. You can take a selfie with her.
Right there and right now, okay?
Savana.
Mister, let me have your phone.
Just one.
Only one picture.
- Savana!
One, two, three...
Mister, smile at the camera.
Look at the camera.
One, two, three...
There. Okay, done.
Okay! Bye!
See you at the meet-and-greet
on her fans' day.
Be present!
Excuse me.
Okay! Hashtag Savana Forever, okay?
- Savana!
Give it to me.
Savana?
Madam, the alcohol is running out.
They say it's not good to be so clean.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
Thank you.
He seems familiar to me.
Who?
The handsome man who asked
for a picture with you?
What?
The one who messed up the wedding scene?
Oh, dear. Do you have a past with him?
It might be another stalker story.
It will only bring trouble.
He was my classmate in college.
He was viral last week!
Look!
I knew it.
I knew it was him!
This is him.
He's the executive of Casa Fuerte,
who almost got stabbed.
- Let me see, let me see.
- There.
I heard people are furious at him
because he's a land grabber.
Is he your college classmate, Savana?
Assassination attempt?
Oh, gosh.
Stay away from him.
Stay away from people like him.
It's a no, no, no, no situation.
That's a no, no, no win-win situation.
- Savana!
Liam Herrera.
Land grabber.
- Rico, let's go.
- Okay, Ma'am Joanne.
- Savana!
[Savana Famous Actress in the Philippines]
[Savana pics]
[Savana TV and Movies]
I feel like I'm just your sister's puppet.
Don't worry.
My sister loves you.
I wish she was as kind as you.
[Savana]
Everything happens for a reason.
What's worse is to spend
the rest of your life with him
and you are not happy.
Tomorrow on Captive Hearts,
before Eat Bulaga!
Hey! That's you, Son!
- Come on, Mom.
- Are you an actor now?
How long have you been standing there?
You seem to have seen a ghost.
No! I'm watching it with you.
When did you join
the filming of Captive Hearts?
I just happened
to be at their shooting location.
I didn't know
they would drag me into the scene.
And what would I do with it?
Me, Son.
I will ask Savana for a video greeting.
Why?
I'm her super fan.
Yes.
I will make my friends envious.
Why does it seem
like a lot of people are obsessed
with Savana?
She's pretty, kind, and a good actress.
Why? Have you met her?
I haven't yet.
But whenever I see her, I'm so fond of her.
It feels like
I have known her for a long time.
What do you mean by that?
She seems so familiar to me.
I feel like we're close.
She's so familiar to me.
She's the type of woman
whom I will cook your favorite adobo for.
A dish I can cook
even when my eyes are closed.
Mom, you're just hungry.
Come on.
I know what to do.
I will cook adobo tomorrow...
For my celebrity son.
I'll leave you for now.
I will call my friends
to tell them to watch Captive Hearts tomorrow.
Everything happens for a reason.
What's worse is
to spend the rest of your life...
Why do you want to kill me?
What? Have you forgotten about me?
That's how rich people are.
You look at poor people like cockroaches...
He seldom spoke when we were in college.
Well, they say silent people are more scary.
I'm old enough! I won't lose anything.
What are you watching, Love?
You look so affected.
Is it good?
What?
The one you're watching.
It's okay,
but I dislike
how the leading man portrays his character.
When did you start watching TV series?
Well... Are you okay? Are you ready?
Let's go?
Why? Are you hungry?
Do you want me to order food?
Love.
You forgot again.
I don't eat at this time. See?
- Intermittent fasting, remember?
- Yeah, right.
Love, thank you.
Is it really okay that you went out with me?
Are you not in a bad mood?
Bad mood? Why?
When you're busy,
you're always in a bad mood.
Is it really okay with you?
Yeah. Of course. No problem.
Thank you, Love!
I think it's a blessing in disguise
that you took leave from Casa Fuerte.
What do you mean?
We have more quality time together.
Right?
Another day is another day!
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who's the fairest of them all?
It's you, Miss Via!
A beautiful morning!
Queenie!
I love your energy.
- Thank you, Miss Via.
- Looks like you had good coffee.
Is everything set?
Have you checked everything?
- Yes, Miss Via!
- Okay.
Our vlog interview for today
is just a mini challenge.
Speaking of, our guest is here.
Savana, you're currently
on top of your league.
Hailed as the Primetime Duchess
of Philippine TV,
Back-to-back Box Office Queen!
What else could Savana ever ask for?
I want to travel to Europe.
Paris.
Paris!
The fashion capital.
So, I assume
you're also into designer brands?
No.
The culture.
I want to experience the culture.
That's why I want to go there so badly.
Whenever I hear that place,
there's unexplainable magic for me.
But fashion, I mean,
it's also part of the Parisian culture.
I'm not into luxury things ever since.
I don't want the overhyped brands.
I have endorsements, a lot, yes.
But I make sure that all the brands I endorse
are accessible to everyone.
So you have this thing for ordinary people?
Oppressed people.
Those who are in need.
I promised from the very start to give voice
to the people who aren't given
a chance to fight.
Those who are at the bottom.
For example,
people whose lands have been grabbed.
That's impressive, Savana.
Maybe your fans admire you
because you're not just a pretty face.
You're also a woman of substance.
That's good.
It's a shame if we don't use
our influence rightly, isn't it?
I agree with you. 100 percent.
I think that's it!
- We're done?
- Yeah, we're done!
Via, thank you so much.
Thank you so much for your time too.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
We're done. We're okay, right, Queenie?
Yes, okay. Pack up!
Everything's okay? I leave everyone to you.
- Yes, Miss Via.
- Where's your assistant?
Shoot.
She's waiting for me in the lobby.
Love.
Savana, I want you
to meet Liam, my boyfriend.
Liam Herrera.
You know each other?
He was at my filming the other day.
You were at Savana's filming, Love?
Yeah.
Actually, I just passed by their location.
You didn't tell me that you've met.
So, better, I guess.
Love, is it okay for you
to walk Savana to the lobby?
Her assistant's there.
I'm so sorry, I can't bring you there.
I still need to supervise the photo shoot.
Thank you again for your time.
Thanks, too.
Queenie, let's go?
Yes, Ma'am.
Savana, wait.
You know my full name?
You were my classmate in Philo 101.
Yes, that's right.
Classmate.
How are you, classmate?
You're in the news.
You're an executive in Casa Fuerte.
And you grabbed the land
of Verde Village's residents, right?
I don't have anything to do with that.
It's your company.
And you don't have anything to do with it?
Do I look like I was born yesterday?
Everything I said in my interview
is all true.
I sympathize with the poor.
If you knew me in college,
you knew I had a difficult life.
And you...
I know you were a scholar.
So I can't understand how you could do that
to the residents of Verde Village.
Whatever our company did, I'm sorry.
You don't need to explain.
I just want to call you out
because what you did is wrong.
Good day, Mr. Herrera.
And you, I know you were a scholar.
So I can't understand how you could do that
to the residents of Verde Village.
Here. You can have it.
Wow. Thanks, Bro.
Don't look at her so much.
She won't come down for you.
Come on. I just find her beautiful.
Have some of this.
No, you can have it.
Of all people who look at that billboard,
you're the only one who looks sad.
Some even took photos of themselves with it.
They're so happy.
They find her so beautiful.
Well, she really is beautiful, anyway.
Well, maybe that's how it goes. Right, Bro?
She's up there, and you're down here.
You can't deny the distance
between you and her.
Do you also watch Joyce's TV show?
Who is Joyce?
Savana, she's my wife.
Right, Love?
Love, are you hungry?
Let's eat.
My good friend here gave us food.
What's your name, Bro?
I'm glad you came back to your senses.
I thought I was no longer
part of Casa Fuerte.
Why did you call me here?
You're right.
You're no longer part of Casa Fuerte
because of what you did.
You know what, Liam?
Our critics see us as
a heartless corporation...
Tough, unwavering, showing no weakness.
What do they know?
Our name, Herrera, means iron works.
Foundry.
Metal that is being molded under high heat.
Pounded to be firm.
Because you can't be soft-hearted
in business.
You need to have iron hands.
That's why a lot will be surprised
by what I'll do.
So I'm giving you a second chance, Liam.
Are you going to reinstate me in Casa Fuerte?
No.
But I'm going to put you
in one of our other companies.
In Blacksmith Productions.
Isn't that Vergil's production house?
Yes.
Why? Is there a problem with that?
No, Dad. But what am I going to do there?
I made you study engineering
after your first degree.
But you wasted it.
I offered you to work
at our construction company many times.
But you turned me down.
Now, you can do whatever you want
in Blacksmith.
But once the situation
in Casa Fuerte becomes okay
and you gain the investors' trust again,
I will reinstate you.
With the way you look,
it seems that you received bad news.
Who would have thought?
Casa Fuerte's wonder boy,
Herrera's prodigal son,
ended up in my company.
Get changed.
Get ready for our meeting
for your first project.
Does it need to be now, Vergil?
From now on, you will call me by my initials.
In Blacksmith, I'm the boss.
You'll address me as VLH.
Hey, you two.
Vergil, make this day productive.
You have a meeting with my good friend.
Don't be late.
Welcome to Blacksmith, Bro.
Via.
Love!
What are you doing here?
My dad told me to come.
He said it was for a meeting.
I think he's taking a movie project.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
And Via will be the head stylist.
She's going to be in charge
of our actors' overall look.
Looks like it's big-budgeted.
Congressman dela Peña!
Vergil.
How are you?
I'm glad my godson,
Tristan's movie project in Blacksmith
will now push through.
It better be a hit.
Tristan's success in the next elections
for congressman
depends on that film.
What can I say?
He looks up to his godfather so much.
Of course, Uncle Ramon.
Well, everything depends
on the creative manager of Tristan's movie.
That's Liam.
So...
This is where Danilo dumped you.
Dad.
I'm excited to meet my next leading lady.
Shall we?
After you, son.
Let's go.
And after all the oppression
the mayor has done,
Leon will rise up from the dead
to save his beloved Jackie
and free his fellowmen.
That's the end of the presentation.
What do you think?
It's an exciting story,
and I can feel the significance of my role.
Wait, how many fight scenes will I have
in the movie?
Three fight scenes, two car chases,
and one long-take rooftop chase
where goons will gang up on you.
Plus, a fight scene while in a helicopter.
Action-packed!
Do I have a love scene here?
What a narcissist.
Vergil, the plot is somehow similar
to my recent film, Tough Guy.
Instead of a politician,
can the villain be a businessman?
We don't want to ruffle feathers.
No problem, Congressman.
The details are not set in stone.
It can still change.
Good thing Liam is here
to take note of the revisions.
Right, Liam?
Good.
Okay, so... Savana, what do you think?
I need time to think.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me for a while.
Savana.
Savana, what drama is this?
I won't do that project, Mom.
Why?
The story isn't good.
Oh, come on.
When did you become picky with projects?
- I won't do it.
- What do you mean?
Tell me why.
Mom, it's because...
Because of Liam and Vergil Herrera.
They're the ones
who grabbed the lands in Verde Village.
What do we have to do with that?
Why?
You know how it feels
to not have a permanent home, Mom.
We get kicked out every month.
And now you want me
to work with those opportunists?
Why? Did they take away your house?
What about my advocacies?
We both know that from the very start,
all I want is to help the oppressed.
Why? Are you planning to run for Congress?
- God, Savana.
- Mom, please listen to me!
No, you listen to me!
If you don't want to lose your house
like the informal settlers you're defending,
go back inside.
Smile and tell them you love the project!
I'll be a hypocrite if I do that, Mom.
I won't work with the Herreras.
You can't back out anymore.
You already signed a contract with Blacksmith
even before the news about Casa Fuerte
broke out.
I can buy my contract.
Listen to me.
This is a big project.
Congressman dela Peña handpicked you
to become the leading lady of this film.
He's an influential man.
Now, I'll give you two choices. You choose.
You'll finish this project
and still have your career,
or you'll go down.
Wrong timing.
Savana won't accept this project anymore.
What made you say that?
- I just feel it.
- We know other actresses.
Oh, anyway, who knows, Congressman...
It's a go.
Good!
I'm glad you accepted the project.
We'll have so much fun.
Looking forward to working with you,
Congressman dela Peña.
The pleasure is mine, dear.
I'm excited to work with you, Savana.
Us, too.
We're excited to work with Blacksmith.
Oh, okay?
Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I didn't expect that Savana
would accept that project.
Why, Boss Bro?
It's work.
I don't know. Something feels off.
Off?
Who wrote that story?
It's so unconvincing.
Leave it be.
Just be grateful that Señor Danilo
didn't fire you after what happened.
But he made me work for my brother.
It's only my first day,
but I want to resign already.
Don't you ever think about that.
Isn't this what you want?
To make a film?
- This is your chance, Boss Bro.
- Not this kind of movie, Borj.
And I can't stand Tristan Perez.
He has an annoying presence.
Right?
You're so silly.
- But what about you, Borj?
- What?
How are you in Casa Fuerte?
I'm currently doing nothing.
Doing nothing?
You mean you're no longer in Casa Fuerte?
Yes.
What's the use of being an assistant
if I have no one to assist, right?
Then you can be my assistant in Blacksmith.
Don't kid me like that, Boss Bro.
You know what I'll say.
Don't you want it? I won't force you.
No, I'll take the job.
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
- Game!
- Maybe you don't want it.
- Just forget about it.
- No, no, no.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- Thank you, Boss Bro!
- Take it easy.
- Thank you!
Do you want coffee?
- Will you pay for it?
- Yes, it's on me.
- Sure. Buy me coffee.
- Boss Bro!
You keep putting your arm on my shoulder.
Come on, Boss Bro. Let's have coffee!
I won't put my arm on your shoulders anymore.
- Go that way.
- I'll buy you coffee.
If you'll pay for it.
Helpless Cindy thanks her savior.
Stop. That's not right.
I need no saving.
We, women, need no saving.
I won't leave you here.
I said go.
I won't go anywhere because I love you!
This is Liam's second favorite.
My mom likes you a lot.
Looks like she's upstaging you.
It seems that she wants to audition
as a daughter-in-law.
So controlling.
Who?
My mom's so controlling
and a terror manager.
Oh my, crocodile!
Have you been here long?
This story has to have a magic typewriter.
What?
The magical typewriter
is the reason why they got separated!